This is an audio course.
Thank you for listening.
And in particular the counterintuitive or surprising
discoveries you've made about courage at work over your
research career?
Well, I think a few insights that have emerged that might
seem counterintuitive, or at least they are counter
to the narrative.
So, for example, I think we have a myth.
In fact, I know we have a myth that courage is some, kind of,
you know, inborn trait or capacity that a few possess,
but most don't.
And, you know, having studied literally thousands of individual
actors and acts of courage,
I can tell you that there is no magic gene.
There's no magic personality trait, background experience.
People who step up and do the right thing at work when they
could and should, very tremendously on every dimension you
and I can name.
So one, sort of, insight or, sort of, myth busting for me has been, it
is not about a personal type, it is about a personal choice.
And I think related to that is that people talk about courageous
action as if, you know, these folks were, sort
of, born ready or it was easy.
But in fact, when you study folks, whether you're talking
about John Lewis, for example, in the political
realm or so many people I studied in,
you know, more regular, kinds of, workplaces,
what you realize is that actually what looks like this natural
competence comes from hard work.
Years of practice, years of trying things,
learning how to be more effective.
So that's the second takeaway, is that this is like any skill.
It's developed through practice and commitment.
Maybe one insight about or about the process itself is we
think a lot about the moment, right?
When somebody speaks up or steps out,
that's the thing we remember and tend to pass on through narrative.
But it turns out that what seems to make a difference in many cases
for how those moments go is the preparation work and the things
people do before those acts,
and then maybe most surprisingly, what they do after. So skillful
actors don't just manage the moment well,
they're really good about after the fact,
following up when things seem to have gone well,
you know, getting commitments, securing resources,
and when things didn't go so well
they're courageous enough to go have yet another difficult
conversation and say,
hey, you know, you look upset or angry or your body
language suggested you weren't on board.
Can we talk about that?
And I think that follow-up is something we don't think much at
all about because we're so focused on that big bang moment itself.